[teacher] Every morning, at the same time,
the same chime echoes through the halls.
[humming]
What a beautiful symbol of harmony.
The empty school building greets me
with its silence.
That is my one and only joy.
[screaming]
[footsteps]
[♪ somber music playing]
[Sawa] Well, then. My house is this way.
Soon, everyone will see it...
That classroom.
Saeki will see it, too.
[chuckling]
I can't wait.
See you.
These pickles are pickled just right.
They taste great.
Stop it.
They're from the store, silly.
[laughs] They are? I couldn't tell.
What are you saying? [chuckles]
Hurry up, Takao, finish up those eggs.
'Kay.
-[Ai] Hey, Nanako...
-[Nanako] Hmm?
I saw something yesterday...
Kasuga and Nakamura were together.
There's something weird going on
between them, Nanako.
[Nanako] Actually, Ai...
I talked to Kasuga yesterday.
He told me
that he wasn't hiding anything from me.
So...
Everything's fine.
[students chattering excitedly]
[♪ tense music playing]
[breath trembling]
[Ai] Kasuga!
You little...
Out of the way!
[Ai sobbing] Nanako, are you all right?
Kasuga, you're her boyfriend, right?
You're supposed to be by Nanako's side!
-[♪ music fades]
-Hey, Kasuga, look at this!
The pervert came back.
-So creepy!
-Shut it, Yamada!
Think about Nanako's feelings!
...IS ME
I'M A DESPICABLE...
[Takao] My name...
It's gone...
[♪ tense, dramatic music playing]
[students chattering indistinctly]
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
[teacher] All right, come on. Settle down!
We're having an emergency assembly
in the gym, so everyone get going!
STYLE
::cue()
Come on, move it!
Let's go, everybody. Come on!
To the gym, please.
Hurry up.
Hey.
Let's go, guys.
Come on, hurry up.
-[♪ music ends]
-To the gym, everyone.
[♪ opening theme music playing]
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
EPISODE 4
We're holding this
emergency school assembly
as the classroom for Second Year Class One
was found vandalized this morning.
I'd like to share what we know.
Last night, near the school...
Those gym clothes...
I bet the pervert used them
in every sexual way imaginable. [laughing]
Hey, Kasuga!
You've got ink on you, right here!
What?
Gotcha! [laughing]
Gotcha! [laughs]
[gags]
[Takao] Restroom...
[Yamada and Kojima snickering]
[Sawa] Kasuga...
are you relieved that your secret is safe?
Man, it's been a while
since I've felt so refreshed!
Did you see their faces?
You should be proud.
You finally peeled back a layer.
[Nanako] Kasuga...
[gags]
[♪ somber music playing]
[breath trembling]
We should break up.
Wait!
That classroom...
and the gym clothes, too.
It was you, wasn't it?
I know because...
On the floor...
was a painting of this flower...
Kasuga!
I told Kasuga for you.
I told him that
you wanted to have sex with him.
What do you mean?
What's going on between you and Kasuga?
I made a contract with him.
Kasuga is a full-blown, hopeless pervert,
so we made a contract
letting me peel back all his layers
until his true self is bare.
-Kasuga isn't a pervert!
-What?
He's a pervert through and through.
You just don't care about who he truly is,
do you, Saeki?
Of course you don't.
All you care about is yourself.
That's not...
[♪ music fades]
STYLE
::cue()
[doorbell rings]
[approaching footsteps]
Takao,
a Ms. Saeki is here to see you.
-[gasping] I can't!
-What?
[Takao] I just can't...
Please.
Tell her I can't see her yet.
Hmm.
I'm sorry,
I think he's still feeling pretty sick.
[Nanako] Right... I see. Thank you.
-[Shizue] Thanks for coming.
-[Nanako] Thank you.
[door opens, closes]
[Nanako] Kasuga!
There's no way I'm breaking up with you!
I'm sorry.
I don't know why you did that, Kasuga.
I can't figure it out...
I don't care about the gym clothes...
I find it flattering!
[♪ gentle music playing]
[Nanako] You did that
because you had feelings for me, right?
More than that, I...
I wish you hadn't hidden things from me!
[sobs]
[breath trembling]
[yelling] So, please tell me!
Not Nakamura, but me.
Help me properly understand
what's going on in your mind!
I'll be waiting for you.
I'll be waiting at that park
where you told me you liked me.
-[♪ music fades]
-[approaching footsteps]
What is going on?
What happened to these?
What have you done?
-[gasping]
-Hey, explain yourself!
[Takao panting]
[coughing]
Took you long enough, Kasuga.
[panting]
There's nowhere...
I can go back to, anymore.
I...
I can't be anywhere in this town anymore.
Not my house,
not my school,
not with Saeki...
[Sawa] 'Kay.
STYLE
::cue()
[Shizue shouting in distance] Takao!
Say something if you're there!
[mumbles]
Takao!
Is that your mother, Kasuga?
How pathetic.
All right then, let's go.
To the other side.
[♪ rising music playing]
Is there any reason for us to stay
in this puke-stained town any longer?
Nakamura,
you're coming with me?
You're tagging along with me,
you barf rat.
[♪ music fades]
[line ringing]
[Shizue's voice] Hello, Kasuga residence.
We are unavailable at the moment.
Please leave a message and your name
after the--
[line ringing]
[man] Hello, Nakamura residence.
[Nanako] Hello, I'm Sawa's classmate.
My name is Saeki and--
Sorry, Sawa isn't home yet.
I see.
Thank you, sir. Have a good night.
[thunderclap]
[rain pattering]
What's wrong? Is everything all right?
I'm going to the stationery store.
I need to get a notebook for tomorrow.
At this hour?
It's raining, you know.
I know it's sudden, I'm sorry.
I'll be right back, though.
-[Seiichi] Sure...
-I'm off.
STYLE
::cue()
[Takao grunting]
[Sawa exclaims]
[Sawa chuckling]
[Takao panting, exclaiming]
I'm completely drenched.
[♪ tense music plays]
What is it?
Uh... Nothing.
I wonder...
what's ahead of here?
I've always wondered.
What if there's nothing on the other side?
That the world just ends there,
and all that's there is black ooze,
just stirring and writhing endlessly.
This sound...
It's like the sound of a town sinking
into a sea of shit bugs.
[rain easing]
[Nanako gasping, panting in distance]
Kasuga!
Saeki...
Why...
[Nanako] Kasuga, I'm sorry.
I backed you into a corner, didn't I?
[♪ slow instrumental music playing]
This book...
I'm sorry.
It got wet.
I read it over and over.
But...
I still don't get it.
Why do you like this book, Kasuga?
What is it like inside your heart?
Please...
tell me.
You and I are dating,
so why do you keep going to Nakamura?
I'm going to the other side.
Kasuga's tagging along.
The other side?
The other side of what?
[♪ music fades]
Kasuga...
Do you...
like Nakamura?
No...
If you want to know so bad, I'll show you.
I'll show you what's inside Kasuga.
Stand up.
Come on, get up!
-Take your clothes off.
-[♪ dramatic music playing]
-Take 'em off!
-[Takao] No, stop!
[yelling] From the moment
he stole your gym clothes,
STYLE
::cue()
I was the one who has been watching him,
this whole time!
Wanna know what he was wearing underneath
when Kasuga confessed his love to you?
The whole time that he was
on that pathetic date with you,
and when he made that lame confession,
he was sniffing and rubbing himself
all over your filthy gym clothes
the whole time,
getting off on them!
He's the kind of pervert
who can lay it all bare!
A true pervert!
-[Sawa grunts]
-[Nanako exclaims]
I didn't rub them on me...
[Nanako] If you did that
out of your feelings for me,
I don't think that you're a pervert.
But be honest with me!
I can take it all...
[sobbing] If there's a version of you
that only Nakamura knows,
I want you to show it all to me!
Let's go back.
Together.
Saeki... [sobbing]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
[♪ somber music playing]
We're done here, Kasuga.
You're so boring.
Go ahead and live in a ditch.
Waste your life here as a shit bug.
[Takao] Nakamura!
[tires squeak]
What is it?
[Nanako running]
[crying] Kasuga!
Am I not enough?
Why are you going after Nakamura?
Do you have feelings for her, after all?
[Sawa] How dumb.
It's really so dumb.
What is?
You don't know a thing about me!
[sobbing] I was really happy.
Kasuga...
turned me from a worthless stone
into a jewel!
[♪ music ends]
Are you coming?
[voice cracking] Or staying?
Please...
don't rip any more holes...
in my soul!
[screams]
[Takao] I...
I'm...
empty.
STYLE
::cue()
-[rain pattering]
-[breath trembling]
I thought everyone else was dumb.
I thought I was different.
But...
Baudelaire...
The Flowers of Evil...
Truth is, I don't really understand it.
I was just in love with myself reading it.
I was trying to look away
from who I really am.
Saeki,
I wanted you to be an angel forever.
I didn't want to face
the actual, real you.
I can't have a normal relationship,
but I'm not a pervert, either!
I can't be the person
that you want me to be, Nakamura.
I've got no substance.
I'm just a despicable shit bug!
I can't choose...
I don't have the right to choose!
Fine...
I'm done.
THE FLOWERS OF EVIL
[sobbing quietly]
[siren blaring]
-[♪ tense music playing]
-[indistinct chatter over radio]
TO BE CONTINUED
[♪ closing theme music playing]
ON THE NEXT EPISODE
[narrator] Kasuga and Nakamura
are unable to escape from this town.
Kasuga ends up
setting foot in the secret garden.
Next time, on episode five.
Kasuga learns the truth about Nakamura.
Translated by Yuka Kristi